Finding Aid for BMC Media Services records, 1851-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
BMC Media Services records
1851-2003
BMC Media Services
93851 BImu C 46 2
BMC Media Services (formerly Biomedical Communications) is an in-house graphics and marketing production service for the University of Michigan. The collection is comprised of visual materials, including photographic prints, negatives, slides, and contact sheets, as well as videotapes, a few films, and digital files. The records reflect BMC's biomedical origins and document the history of the medical school, health science, hospitals, and related departments at the University of Michigan.
31.6 linear feet in 35 boxes
3 films, oversize rolled materials and oversize folders
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group was initially received through the Historical Center for Health Sciences in 1992 (Donor 8111 ). Periodic additions are received from BMC (Donor No. 8110 ).
Periodic additions to the records expected.
Restricted access in part; see access restrictions on following page.
The BMC record group includes restricted material in the following categories:
Student Academic Records -- removed to vault storage.
BMC Media Services, formerly Biomedical Communications, was an in-house graphics and marketing production service for the University of Michigan. Owing to its medical origins, BMC Media Services was administratively a unit in the Department of Medical Education within the University of Michigan Medical School. In the mid 1960s the Medical Photography, Medical Television, and Medical Illustration units in the Medical School were consolidated to form the Biomedical Media Production Unit (BMPU). In 1983 BMPU changed its name to Biomedical Communications. By the late 1990s the biomedical aspect was de-emphasized in favor of BMC Media Services, a recognition of the broader role the unit played on campus.
In 2006, the University's two marketing organizations, BMC Media services and Marketing Communications, merged to form Michigan Marketing and Design (MM&D). Marketing Communications had provided print and Web publishing and creative service across the central academic and administrative units while BMC Media services primarily served the U-M Health System and provided video production, in addition to print and Web-based services.
Michigan Marketing and Design provides communications consulting and strategic planning; creative concept development and messaging, graphic design and production, web design and production services.
The records of BMC Media Services (formerly Biomedical Communications) measure 31.65 linear feet of visual material in a variety of formats. The records consist of seven series, largely different photographic categories: Faculty and Staff Portraits, Group Portraits, Class Photographs, Building Photographs, Topical Photographs, Films, and Videotapes.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. Medical School.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Child, Charles Gardner, 1908-; Health facilities--Design and construction.; Hospitals--Design and construction.; Medicine--Michigan.; Surgery.; University of Michigan. Medical School.; University of Michigan. Hospitals.; University of Michigan. Replacement Hospital Project.; University of Michigan--Students.Students.; University of Michigan. Medical School--Faculty.Faculty.; Medical education--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Barnard, Christiaan, 1922-2001
Genre/Form:
Motion pictures.; Photographs.; Videotapes.
- Faculty and Staff Portraits
  The Faculty and Staff Portraits series (9.15 linear feet) consists of an alphabetically arranged run of individual photographs, somewhat arbitrarily subdivided by letter, and a subseries of Individual Portraits by Department, arranged alphabetically by department. The Individual Portraits by Subjects sub-series consists primarily of black and white negatives and copy prints of medical faculty and staff, both professional and administrative. BMC collected the earlier photographic material which includes some copies made from late 19th and early 20th century sources. The sub-series is arranged alphabetically by surname. There are generally more negatives than prints, and the majority are studio portraits. Many of the folders include additional information regarding individuals, such as the units with which they were affiliated at the University of Michigan. The Individual Portraits by Department sub-series consists of black and white and color negatives and contact prints, and some copy prints of medical faculty, staff, and students. In instances where separate negatives, photographs, or contact sheets did not exist for individuals, they are arranged by department. Examples of this include negative strips, contact sheets, and negatives that contain images of numerous individuals within a department. The photographic material in the Individual Portraits sub-series dates from the latter half of the twentieth century, and the majority of it was most likely produced by BMC.
  - A-C
    - Aaronson, Keith, Cardiology, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Abbott, Leroy Charles, undated (Box 1)
    - Abdulrazzak, Mamdouh, Neurology, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Abel, John Jacob, undated (Box 1)
    - Abela, Andrew, Oral Surgery, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Abell, Murray, Pathology, 1953; 1955; 1958; 1963 (Box 1)
    - Abernathy, William S., Internal Medicine, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Abicht, Hikka, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Abrams, Gerald D., 1958; 1972; 1987; undated (Box 1)
    - Adams, Barbara Pediatrics, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Adams, Douglass, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Adams, Kristine, Immunology, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Adams, Paul, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Advincula, Arnold, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Afr, Nancy, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1996 (Box 1)
    - Albers, (?), 1997 (Box 1)
    - Albers, James, Neurology, 1999; 2000; undated (Box 1)
    - Aldridge, Wayne, Neurology, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Alessi, Norman, Psychiatry, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Alexander, (?), undated (Box 1)
    - Alexander, John, Thoracic Surgery, 1940s; undated (Box 1)
    - Al-Harthi, Abdulaziz, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Allen Eagle, Kim, Cardiology, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Allen, (?), Radiology, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Allen, Richard J., Pediatrics circa 1957, 1959, 1968, 1975 (includes photograph of Allen with Donald Malkoff) (Box 1)
    - Allison, John, 1971 (Box 1)
    - Allmand, Charles, Personnel, 1953; 1955 (Box 1)
    - Almedo, (?), Neurosurgery, circa 1958 (Box 1)
    - Alozie, Chidinma, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Alpern, Mathew, 1970; undated (Box 1)
    - Al-Saadi, Abdul A., 1969 (Box 1)
    - Altenau, Lance L., Neurosurgery, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Amiroff, (?), undated (Box 1)
    - Amoura, Nahia Jean, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 1)
    - Anderson, (?), Physical Medicine, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, David (includes wife) circa 1958, 1960 Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1965, 1973, undated (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Stephanie, Bone Marrow Transplant Programs, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, William, CNL, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Angell, James Burrill, undated (Box 1)
    - Ansbacher, Rudi, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1996; undated (Box 1)
    - Anuszkiewicz, Shelli, Bone Marrow Transplant Programs, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Anzai Yoshini, Radiology, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Arenberg, Doug, IM-Pulmonary, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Armstrong, Robert, 1929 (Box 1)
    - Armstrong, William C., undated (Box 1)
    - Armstrong, William, Internal Medicine, Cardiology, 1992; 1998; 2000; 2001 (Box 1)
    - Attar, Mohammad, Pediatrics 1997 2000Augenstein, Kim, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Augustine, Joe, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Avidan, Alon, Neurology, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Ayash, Lois, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1997; 1999 (Box 1)
    - Ayers, Jonathan, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Azram, Anca, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Baas, Arnold, Internal Medicine, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Bacon, George E., 1975 (Box 1)
    - Badgley, Carl E. (includes wife), 1949; 1953; 1956; 1958; 1961; 1967; undated (Box 1)
    - Bae, Jeehyeon -- Viquie, Reproductive Science, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Bagchi, Basu K., 1956; 1967 (Box 1)
    - Baghdoyan, Helen, Anesthesiology, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Bailey, (?), 1981 (Box 1)
    - Bailey, Robert W. (includes wife), 1951; 1954; 1957; 1964; 1970 (Box 1)
    - Baird, Lillian G., 1956; 1964 (Box 1)
    - Baker, Burton L., undated (Box 1)
    - Baker, James, Pediatrics, Medical Center Development, 1994; 1997; 2000 (Box 1)
    - Baker, Joyce, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Baker, Randy, Family Practice, undated (Box 1)
    - Baker, Vicky, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995; 1996 (Box 1)
    - Ballak, Zita, Nuclear Medicine, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Bandera, Pediatrics, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Barclay, Mel, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Barclay, Beth, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Barkan, Ariel, L. Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Barker, P., 1998 (Box 1)
    - Barker, Paul S. (see also Furstenberg), circa 1949 (Box 1)
    - Barlow, Peter B., 1968; undated (Box 1)
    - Barnard, Rene, Pharm, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Barnard, Ruth, Nursing, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Barnhart, Douglas, General Surgery, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Barnwell, John B., 1932 (Box 1)
    - Barr, Mason, Pediatrics, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Barragry, Thomas, Thoracic Surgery, undated (Box 1)
    - Barrett, Albert Moore, circa 1900s (Box 1)
    - Barrigar, Eileen, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Barry, Alexander M., 1967 (Box 1)
    - Barsan, William, Emergency Medicine, undated (Box 1)
    - Bartlett, Robert H., General Surgery, 1996; 1998; 2000 (Box 1)
    - Baruch, El-CNL Protocol, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Bashur, Rashid, Medical Center Development, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Batchelor (?), Ann, Heart Care Program (Box 1)
    - Bates, Eric, Cardiology, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Bates, R. C., undated (Box 1)
    - Batsakis, John, 1958; 1959; 1972 (Box 1)
    - Baublis, Joseph V., 1973; undated (Box 1)
    - Bayliss, G., Rheumatology, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Bean, John W., Physiology, 1965; 1973; undated (Box 1)
    - Beardslee, Lelah, circa 1958 (Box 1)
    - Beaudoin, Allan R., Anatomy and Cell Biology, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Beck, Jim, Internal Medicine, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Beekman, Kathleen, Internal Medicine, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Beeman, Holly, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Beers, Allan, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 1)
    - Behrendt, Douglas M., 1985; undated (Box 1)
    - Behrman, Samuel Jon, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1952; 1955; 1959; 1960; 1962; 1973; 1977 (Box 1)
    - Beierwaltes, William (includes wife), 1953; 1959; 1978; undated (Box 1)
    - Belcher, Lisa, Nursing, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Bemer, Julia, Family Medicine, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Bender, Leonard F. (includes wife), Physical Medicine, 1958; 1961; 1968; 1974 (Box 1)
    - Bentz, Rodney, Internal Medicine, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Benudi (?), Sue, Gastro, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Berent, Stanley, Psychology, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Berger, Candyce, Social Work, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Bergin, (?), Cardiology, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Bergman, Cynthia, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Berkowitz, Sharon, Primary Care, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Bernstein, Isadore A., Dermatology, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Bethell, Frank, Internal Medicine, circa 1949; 1958 (Box 1)
    - Bethune, Norman (copy), circa 1935 (Box 1)
    - Bett, Karen, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Betz, A. Lorris, Dean's Office, 1996 (Box 1)
    - Beydoun, Ahmad, Neurology, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Bieliauskas, Linas, Psychiatry, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Bigongiari, Lawrene R., Radiology, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Billi, John E., Medical Administration, undated (Box 1)
    - Billings, Heather, Reproductive Sciences, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Binno, Shereen, Obstetrics and Gynecology, Primary Care, 1996; 2001; undated (Box 1)
    - Bird, C.W., Psychiatry, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Bishop, Keith, Microbiology and Immunology, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Bishop, Ronald C., 1972 (Box 1)
    - Blackmore, Diane, Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Blair, Donald, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Blair, Joseph, Nuclear Medicine, undated (Box 1)
    - Blane, Caroline, Radiology, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Blatt, Neal, Chemistry, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Blaum, Caroline, Medical School Administration, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Bleisner, Siri, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Bliss, Sandy, Internal Medicine, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Block, Walter, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Bloom, (?), 1990 (Box 1)
    - Bloom, David, Urology, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Blumer, Neal, Social Work, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Blumstein, Sylvie, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Bohnen, Nicholaas, Nuclear Medicine, 1996 (Box 1)
    - Bohr, David F., Physiology, 1957; 1961; 1972 (Box 1)
    - Bole, Giles G., Internal Medicine, 1960; 1962; 1971; 1972; 1990 (Box 1)
    - Boles, Libby, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Bolling, Steve, Thoracic Surgery, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Bolt, Robert J., 1964; 1972 (Box 1)
    - Bolton, Stephanie, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Bomar, Francine, Family Medicine, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Bondy, Kerry, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Bonnette, Gerald H., Oral Surgery, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Bookstein, Fred L., Institute of Gerontology, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Bookstein, Joseph J., Radiology, 1960; 1967; 1972 (Box 1)
    - Booth, Dorothy, Nursing, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Borschel, Tina, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Boulet, Daniel, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Boulis, Nick, Neurosurgery, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Bove, Edward L., Alumni and Development, Medicine at Michigan, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Bower, Cynthia, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Bowers, Lee, Internal Medicine, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Bowman, Phillip, Psychiatry, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Boxer, Laurence, Pediatric Hematology, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Boyd, Anne, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Boyd, Carol, Nursing, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Bozoki, Andrea, Neurology, 1998; 1999 (Box 1)
    - Braden, Spencer, undated (Box 1)
    - Bradley, David, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Bradley, Kathryn, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 1)
      (see Downing, Mary, Anesthesiology, 1997
    - Bragdon, Jeremy, MCD (Box 1)
    - Brammer, Robert E., Otology, Neurotology, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Brandt, Mary-Margaret, General Surgery, Trauma Burn Center, undated (Box 1)
    - Brass, Alan W., 1978 (Box 1)
    - Braun, Ann, Alumni and Development, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Breakey, James, undated (Box 1)
    - Breakey, William F., undated (Box 1)
    - Bree, Max M., Unit for Laboratory and Animal Medicine, 1967; 1974 (Box 1)
    - Brenner, Dean, Internal Medicine and Oncology, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Brewer, George, Human Genetics, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Briggs, Josephine, Internal Medicine, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Brody, Jerry, 1951; 1954; 1956; 1958 (Box 1)
    - Brosius, Frank "Chip," Nephrology, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Brown, Elisa, Neurology, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Brown, Ann, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Brown, Dionne, Trauma Burn, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Brown, Naki, Reproductive Science, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Brown, Randall, Pediatrics, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Brown- Proctor, Clive, Nuclear Medicine, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Bruce, J. D., Medical School Dean, undated (Box 1)
    - Bryan, Ted, Nuclear Medicine, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Btaiche, Imad, Pharmacy, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Buchman, Steven, Plastic Surgery, Medical School Administration, 1997; 2000 (Box 1)
    - Bufatola(?), Psychiatry, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Bull, Frances E., Internal Medicine, 1987; 1989 (Box 1)
    - Buono, Nicole, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Burant, Charles, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Burd, C., Ro, undated (Box 2)
    - Burke, James J., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Burkel, William, Anatomy, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Burney, Richard, Medical Center Development, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Burrows, Heather, Alumni Development, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Burton, Marion L., undated (Box 2)
    - Byrant, Henry C. Jr., 1970 (Box 2)
    - Byrkit, Ramona, School of Public Health, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Cabana, Michael, Primary Care, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Cabot, Hugh, 1929 (Box 2)
    - Calarco, Margaret, Hospital Administration, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Caldwell, Cleopatra, School of Nursing, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Calhoun, Gary, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Calhoun, Judy, 1979; 1984 (Box 2)
    - Camp, Carl D., Neurology, undated (Box 2)
    - Campbell, (?), 1989 (Box 2)
    - Campbell, Colin, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1972; undated (Box 2)
    - Campbell, David, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Campos, Jose L., Radiology, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Candido, Kim, General Surgery, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Candy, (?), Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 2)
    - Canfield, Roy Bishop, undated (Box 2)
    - Caoili, Elaine, Radiology, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Cardneau, Jeff, Surgery, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Carey, Thomas, Otolaryngology, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Carlos, Ruth, Radiology, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Carlson, Bruce, 1996 (Box 2)
    - Carnahan, Donna Anesthesiology 1997 see Stump, Larry, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Carpenter, Glenn B., 1957; 1958 (Box 2)
    - Carr, Edward A. Jr., Internal Medicine, 1974; undated (Box 2)
    - Carrello, Patrice, Psychology, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Carroll, (?), Allergy, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Carson, Erik, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Carter-Su, Christin, Physiology, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Casey, Kenneth L., Neurology, Physiology, 1972; 1999 (Box 2)
    - Cassidy, James T., 1976 (Box 2)
    - Castelli, Walter, Anatomy, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Castor, C. William, 1975; undated (Box 2)
    - Cather, Jane R., Pathology, undated (Box 2)
    - Cease, Kemp, Internal Medicine, 2000; 2001 (Box 2)
    - Cedurna, Paul, Plastic Surgery, 1997; undated (Box 2)
    - Cerny, Joseph C., Urology, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Chang, (?), undated (Box 2)
    - Chang, Annette, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Chapman, Daniel, M-Works, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Chardenet, Kathleen, Anesthesiology, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Charpie, John, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Chen, (?), 1989 (Box 2)
    - Chen, (?), Surgery, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Chenowith, Jim, Family Practice, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Cherven, Laura, Nursing, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Chervin, Ron, Neurology, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Chey, William, Internal Medicine, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Chien, Alexander, Radiology, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Child, Charles G. III, Surgery, 1958; 1972; 1975; undated (Box 2)
    - Chiodo, Tony, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Cho, Kathleen, Pathology, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Chong, Bui, Radiology, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Christensen, A. Kent, Histology, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Christenson, Halvor N., Biochemistry, 1972; 1973; 1977; undated (Box 2)
    - Christman, Gregory Michael, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Christy, Adwoa, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 2)
    - Chrite, Brent, Business School, undated (Box 2)
    - Chudnofsky, Carl, Medical Center Development, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Chug, Rashmy, Internal Medicine, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Chung, Ming, Nursing, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Cichon, Jack, Urology, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Clarke, Michael, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Cleland, Michelle, Primary Care, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Cleveland, Robert O., 1949; 1954 (Box 2)
    - Clipson, Thea, Reproductive Science, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Cody, Robert, Cardiology, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Cole, Theodore, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1978; 1999 (Box 2)
    - Coller, Frederick J., 1937; 1941; 1950; 1955; 1957; undated (Box 2)
    - Collins, Francis, Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 1990; 1991 (Box 2)
    - Comstock, (?), undated (Box 2)
    - Condon, Robert, Physical Medicine, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Conlon, Paul, Pharmacology, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Conn, Jerome, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1966; 1967; 1970; 1971; undated (Box 2)
    - Consens, Flavia, Neurology, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Cook, Steven, Psychiatry, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Cooke, Jim, Medical School Administration, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Cooke, Kevin, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Coon, Minor Jud, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Coon, William, Surgery, 1965; undated (Box 2)
    - Cooney, Kathy, Hematology and Oncology, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Coran, Arnold, Pediatric Surgery, 1998; 2000; undated (Box 2)
    - Cornish, Laura, Pharmacy, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Corssen, Guenter, Anesthesiology, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Coscia, Arthur (includes wife), Medical Records, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Counsell, Raymond, Pharmacology, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Cowie, David Murray, undated (Box 2)
    - Cowles, Robert, Surgery, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Cowley, Collin, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Coy, Rob, Med Sport, 1993 (Box 2)
    - Craig, Holly, Communication Disorders 1997 see Hackley, Communication Disorders, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Craig, Anita, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Craig, Holly, Professor of Education, Research Professor, Institute for Human Adjustment, Director, University Center for the Development of Language and Literacy, undated (Box 2)
    - Crane, Augustus W., undated (Box 2)
    - Crane, Patricia, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 2)
    - Crofford, Leslie, Internal Medicine, 1999; undated (Box 2)
    - Crosby, Elizabeth, Anatomy, 1931; 1953; 1969; 1970; 1971; undated (Box 2)
    - Cross, Cynthia, Rackham Graduate School, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Cross, Thomas N., 1961 (Box 2)
    - Crowley, Dennis, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Csete, Marie, Anesthesiology, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Cummings, Howard H., undated (Box 2)
    - Cummings, Vera, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Cunningham, Amy, School of Public Health, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Cupchak, Mary Jo, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Curtis, Arthur, 1955; 1967; 1972; undated (Box 2)
    - Cushing, Arthur, undated (Box 2)
  - D-E
    - D'Alecy, Louis, 2001 (Box 2)
    - D'Angelo, Andrea, Internal Medicine, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Dabich, Lyubica, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Dalston, Jeptha, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Dalton, Vanessa, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997; 2001 (Box 2)
    - Daly, Thomas J., Ambulatory Care Administration, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Darling, C.G., undated (Box 2)
    - Das, Sunil K., 1962; 1973 (Box 2)
    - Datta, Prasanta, Biological Chemistry, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Daughenbaugh, Michael, Environmental Services, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Davenport, Charles W., Psychology, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Davenport, Fred M., 1951 (Box 2)
    - Davenport, Horace W., Physiology, 1967; 1973; 1974 (Box 2)
    - Davenport, Jason, Family Medicine, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Davey, Winthrop N., 1958; 1972; undated (Box 2)
    - Davidson, Frances H., Registrar, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Davies, Pamela, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Davis, (?), 1969 (Box 2)
    - Davis, (?), Hypertension, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Davis, Matthew, Primary Care, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Davis, Steve, Oral Surgery, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Davis, Tony, Neurology, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Davidson, Eleanor, Family Practice, undated (Box 2)
    - Davis, Wayne, 1976; 1985; undated (Box 2)
    - Dawson, David, Medical School Administration, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Day, Mark, Urology,1996 (Box 2)
    - Day, Stephanie, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Dayanikli, B. Firat, Internal Medicine, undated (Box 2)
    - Deaner, Stephanie, Psychology, 1999 (Box 2)
    - DeAngelo, (?), 1984 (Box 2)
    - DeClercq, Tana, Medical School Administration, 2001 (Box 2)
    - DeJong, Russell N. (includes family), Neurology, 1951; 1954; 1956-1958; 1964 (Box 2)
    - DeJonge, Bud, Neurosurgery, 1960; 1965; 1968; undated (Box 2)
    - DeKornfeld, Thomas J., Anesthesiology, 1967; 1984; 1986; undated (Box 2)
    - DeLancey, John O. L., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Del Monte, Monte A., Ophthalmology, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Del Valle, John, Internal Medicine, 2000; 2001 (Box 2)
    - Delaney, Donna, Neurology, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Deledda, John, Medical Center Development, 1999 (Box 2)
    - De Leon, Richard, Pharmacology, undated (Box 2)